<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>
    <string-array name="ans1">
        <item>OnCreate(),OnStart(),OnResume(),OnPause(),OnStop(),OnDestroy(),OnRestart()</item>
        <item>Android-based devices have a collection of built-in sensors in them, which measure certain parameters like motion, orientation, and many more through their high accuracy. The sensors can be both hardware and software based on nature. There are three prominent categories of sensors in Android devices.</item>
        <item>The AndroidManifest.xml file contains information regarding the application that the Android system must know before the codes can be executed.
This file is essential in every Android application.
It is declared in the root directory.
This file performs several tasks such as: Providing a unique name to the java package.</item>
        <item>Class is a compiled form of a .java file that Android uses to produce an executable .apk file.
A file is a block of arbitrary information or resources used for storing information. It can be of any file type</item>
        <item>Toast is a message that pops up on the screen. It is used to display the message regarding the status of the operation initiated by the user and covers only the expanse of space required for the message while the user’s recent activity remains visible and interactive.

Toast notification automatically fades in and out and it does not accept interaction events.</item>
        <item>ANR(Application is Not Responding) is a dialog box that appears when the application is not responding. This ANR dialogue is displayed whenever the main thread within an application has been unresponsive for a long time under the following conditions:

When there is no response to an input event even after 5 seconds.When a broadcast receiver has not completed its execution within 10 seconds.</item>
        <item>Containers carry objects and widgets together, based on which specific items are required and in what particular arrangement is needed. Containers may hold labels, buttons, fields, or even child containers, etc. For example, if you want a form with fields on the left and labels on the right, you will need a container. If you want the OK and Cancel buttons to be below the rest of the form, next to one another, and flush to the right side of the screen, you will need a container. If you have several widgets, you will need a container to have a root element to place the widgets inside.</item>
        <item>Dalvik serves as a virtual machine, and it is responsible for running every Android application. Because of Dalvik, a device will have the ability to execute multiple instances of virtual machines efficiently through better memory management.</item>
    </string-array>
</resources>